[ominous music playing]
[wind whistling]
[owl hooting]
[podcaster 1] What do you even
have to back it up?
[podcaster 2] There were eyewitnesses.
A man fitting Macher's description
was spotted at a sorority party
at Windsor College in 1997.
The same year the murders took place.
[podcaster 1 scoffs]
It's complete speculation,
all right? That's never been confirmed.
[podcaster 2] It has been con--
[sighs]
Holy shit.
[passenger] Ugh, that was a long drive.
[driver chuckles]
Holy fucking shit!
Can you get a photo of me?
Yeah.
All right. Cute.
[shutter clicking]
[shouts]
[passenger chuckles]
- I got it.
- [chuckles]
Wait, one more. One more.
[groans]
Okay, I have to pee. Let's go inside.
- The code is...
- [sighs, groans]
...7-8-2-2.
[lock clicks]
[chuckles]
- Are you ready for...
- [lock clicking]
...the Macher House Experience?
Wow.
- Oh.
- [switch clicks]
- Oh, my God.
- Ugh.
- Incredible.
- Whoa.
[driver chuckles]
A real-life murder house.
- It's perfect.
- [sighs]
- Mm-hmm.
- Right?
I mean, it's like-- it's identical.
Oh, this is cool.
- The fake blood.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh! [driver laughs]
Check it out. Check it out.
[groans]
Ugh, I'm gonna pee my pants.
- [imitates gagging]
- [shutter clicks]
Babe, this is where Sidney Prescott
shot Billy Loomis in the face
right after she--
Stabbed him with the umbrella. I know.
Where's the bathroom?
Oh, no, that's the closet
Sidney was hiding in.
Remember? Before she stabbed
him with the umbrella?
Duh.
[sighs]
Oh, I found it!
Oh. [chuckles]
So cool.
Ah.
This is so cool!
Incredible.
Amber.
And Richie. I mean...
[shutter clicks]
Ooh.
[footsteps receding]
Scott?
[ominous music plays]
Hello?
Scott!
Dude, where'd you go?
[metal clinking]
[screams]
[breathing heavily]
[both scream]
- Whoa. What's wrong?
- Oh, my God! Ghostface is in there!
- What? What are you--
- Ghostface is in there!
Someone with a ghost mask on.
What are you talking about?
There's somebody in that room
with a Ghostface mask on.
Oh...
[breathes shakily] Do not go in there.
Scott. Scott!
[ominous music plays]
- [gasps]
- Ooh!
- You're going to die tonight!
- [chuckles]
It's fake.
Oh, that is so cool.
It's got a motion sensor.
Look at this.
Do you like scary movies?
[Scott] I mean, come on, look at that.
- [sensor whirring]
- That's so cool.
Pretty hi-tech.
It looked so real.
That is sweet!
Wow.
- It's plugged in right here.
- What?
- Ah, so this is it.
- This is so creepy.
The room where Stu held that party
to lure Sidney Prescott to her death.
You know, they say Billy
was the mastermind,
but I've always been more of a Stu-head.
- Who was your favorite?
- What?
My favorite homicidal teenager?
Neither.
Are you gonna be like this the whole time?
What do you want me to do?
[mutters] Um...
Okay. Babe, did you know that this is
where Sidney dropped a TV on Stu's head?
Squished all the crazy out of his brain?
Ah, but did she kill him?
You heard the podcast.
There's a lot of theories out there
that Stu survived.
[passenger] No. There was a dead body.
It was taken to the morgue
and then buried.
- [hums]
- You can't fake that.
Let's check out the kitchen.
Ooh.
Oh, this is where Sidney and Gale Weathers
roasted Amber Freeman a few years ago.
Yeah, where she was torched. [sighs]
I would hate to die that way.
[gasps]
- Oh, my God.
- It's fake.
It's fake. [chuckles]
Fucking hilarious.
[phone rings]
It's happening.
- [line beeps]
- Hello?
[voice on phone]
Hello, Scott. Hello, Madison.
Welcome to the Macher House Experience.
Enjoying it so far?
- It's amazing.
- Mm-hmm.
Do you like scary movies?
Go, go.
Uh, yeah, my boyfriend's a big horror fan.
What's your favorite scary movie?
- Stab One.
- It's time to play a game.
Scary Movie Trivia. Three questions.
Get one wrong, and you die. Question one:
In the original A Nightmare on Elm Street,
who is the first person to die?
- Tina Gray.
- Correct.
Question two:
In The People Under the Stairs,
what's the name of
Mommy and Daddy's daughter?
- Alice.
- Very good.
Let's try a hard one this time.
In Friday the 13th,
how old was Jason Voorhees
when he drowned?
Okay, well, in The Final Chapter
we found out Mrs. Voorhees
gave birth in 1946, right?
And then in the original,
the two counselors died
in the flashback in '58.
Jason drowned the summer before that.
That's '57.
So born in '46, drowned in '57.
Eleven. Jason was eleven.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Scott,
but that's incorrect.
Bullshit. No, the math was right.
It's a trick question.
Jason never drowned.
Very impressive, Madison.
Scott's lucky he has you to lean on.
I guess I don't get to stab
you guys after all. [chuckles]
You two have a chilling night.
And don't forget to give us a five-star--
Are you miserable?
I wish I could fake it better.
Why'd you come here with me?
Well, you were pushy about it!
And I thought I could be cool,
then we got here and it's so cheesy.
You want to go?
I don't want to be here if you don't.
I can drive home right now.
You would drive home right now?
I would.
No, it's too late.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna try harder. I promise.
Okay, now I have to pee.
- It's the hallway on the left.
- [chuckles]
[exhales, smacks lips]
[sighs]
[phone rings]
Hello?
[caller] You're going to die tonight.
Scott, why are you calling me?
[caller] It's not Scott.
Okay.
Who is it then?
[caller] The person who's gonna kill you.
The scary voice thing is
a little bit sexy,
but you could work on it.
[caller] Listen, you little bitch,
I'm gonna slice you open
and rip your guts out!
Did you just call me a bitch?
Okay, I said I would try,
but I'm done. This isn't fun.
[caller] Because the fun part
is over, Madison.
[line beeps]
[object thuds]
Scott?
They'd never make it in time.
Scott!
We're not finished yet.
Fuck you!
Stu--
[gasps, screams]
[Scott groans] Ow! Ow!
- It's me.
- What the fuck?
- [groans] You hit me.
- What is wrong with you?
I'm sorry. I thought it...
- [panting]
- [gasps]
You said you were gonna try.
[stutters] It was a bad idea.
Yeah, of course it was a bad fucking idea!
It moved.
Yeah, it's electric. That's what it does.
No. Like, it moved
differently.
[Madison] What?
- Oh!
- [Madison screams]
[Scott grunts, groans]
[gasps] No!
[screams, sobs]
[screams]
[panting]
[screaming]
[screams]
Fuck you! [screams]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[screams]
[grunting, breathing heavily]
[screams, pants]
[screams]
[flesh squelches]
[grunting, panting]
[groans]
[quiet, high-pitched ringing]
[clattering]
[muttering weakly]
[flames roar]
[whimpering, groaning]
No! No, no, no. No, no, no. [cries]
[sobbing]
[screaming]
[glass shatters]
[dramatic music playing]
[phone ringing]
[screaming]
["Criminal" playing]
[typing]
[phone chimes]
[crunching]
[ominous music plays]
[screams]
Jesus, you scared me.
You're gonna give me a heart attack.
- I'm sorry.
- What are you doing here?
Well...
it occurred to me that I've never
snuck through your bedroom window.
I was home, bored,
watching TV...
Mmm.
...and Stab was on.
And that just got me thinking of you.
That's horrific.
Billy snuck through Sidney's window, so...
Mm-hmm. I'm well aware.
You know, if my mom catches you...
Mmm. Just a kiss.
Hey.
Hi.
- [knocking on door]
- [boyfriend] Oh!
[body thuds]
[door opens]
Can you knock?
I did.
Can you wait for a response?
Something wrong?
No.
- No, everything's fine.
- You sure?
Mm-hmm.
Ben, how you doing over there?
On the floor. Behind the bed.
Hello, Mrs. Evans.
How are you this evening?
Oh, well, I'm tired. Ben, it's late.
That's why I didn't want to
disturb anyone by...
using the door.
So thoughtful.
Out.
- But he's here now.
- No.
That's okay. I'm going.
Good night, Tate.
[Ben] I know it's late.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Evans.
That was on me.
Tatum had no idea that I was coming over.
Okay, well, let's not do it again.
[sighs]
I'm a good guy, Mrs. Evans.
Good night, Ben.
Hypocrite.
[scoffs]
It's not like a boy's never
crawled through your window.
- [phone chimes]
- We've all seen the movie.
Which is why it's never
gonna happen in this house.
Why do you not like him?
[sighs]
I don't not like him.
I just-- I want you to be smart.
And not trust him so easily.
We're not having sex,
if that's what you're worried about.
I mean, we want to,
but I don't think we're ready.
Well, if you're asking
the question, then, um...
you're probably not.
How did you know?
I mean, did that really happen to you?
Like in the movie?
It's freezing in here.
[Sidney exhales]
How about we have
these kinds of conversations
during waking hours, okay?
No more boys in windows, please.
[Sidney sighs]
Night.
[sighs]
How ugly did it get?
I was extremely polite.
You know, she's not the first girl
to let a boy sneak in her window.
Yeah. She made that point.
You know, if being an overprotective mom
is the worst thing she can
say about me... [sighs]
...I think I can live with that.
You think they're doing it?
Oh, God, no.
[chuckles] No. Not yet.
But I think we've got
about five minutes left.
How old were you when you started?
Same age as you. Seventeen.
Oh, did I say seventeen?
I think I meant fifteen.
Did you lie to me?
Look, in my defense, I don't remember.
Oh, you don't remember
the first time you had sex?
Oh, no, I don't remember what I told you.
Oh, you told me seventeen.
Look, I didn't want to
come off as, you know...
Uh-huh. Keep going.
I want to see where this goes.
[stammers] I just wanted you to see me
as more than a sex slave.
Oh. You have a mind, too?
You know... well, yeah.
[gentle music playing]
[people chuckling]
[rock music playing]
[saw whirring]
[people chattering indistinctly]
[contractor] Morning, Chief.
Hey, Woody. Look at that,
the walls are up, right?
Looks great.
- [child on tablet] Love you.
- I love you, too. We miss you guys.
- [Mark] Construction's coming along.
- We're keeping them busy.
- Oh. Hey, Mom.
- [mother] Hi there, baby.
- [child] Hi, Daddy.
- Thanks, Junie.
I'm glad you're having fun.
- If you need anything, call.
- Okay.
I love you. Thank you
for watching the maniacs.
We'll see you this weekend.
- Bye.
[tablet chimes]
- She's very brave.
- Yep.
- [ominous music plays]
- [saw whirs]
What?
Where'd you find that?
Um, the attic.
I was looking through some old clothes.
Do you not want me to wear it?
You could have asked.
Honey, maybe take it off.
What age do they get nice again?
That was on you.
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
[mysterious music plays]
You can wear the jacket.
It's okay, I'm good.
Tatum, I'm sorry.
Okay? It caught me off guard.
I hadn't seen it since college.
I thought I'd gotten rid of it.
Yeah, the mysterious one semester
at Windsor we can't talk about.
That's not true.
Really? Since when?
Your childhood is completely off-limits.
[laughs] What are you talking about?
It's not off-limits.
It's online and in movies and in books.
You could do a deep dive
whenever you want.
As long as I don't ask questions.
You have rehearsal today?
Yep.
How's it going?
Horrible.
Tragic. [chuckles]
I get so nervous onstage,
it's painful to watch.
Oh, God! I used to get stage fright.
I know the feeling.
You did theater?
Not since college.
Anyway, don't worry.
You're gonna do great.
I got to get to work.
Fucking motherhood.
Great talk.
["The Kill" playing]
["The Kill" continues through speakers]
- Morning.
- Hey, morning.
[server] We'll have that
right out for you. Okay?
[customer] All right. Thank you.
- Busy?
- Little AM rush, but not too bad.
Good. [sighs]
- Hey, Mrs. Evans.
- Hey, Lucas.
Oh, could I get
four espresso shots, please?
Yeah. For sure.
- Four?
- Yeah. [chuckles]
Rehearsal today. It's gonna be a long one.
What part do you play?
Oh, just a techie. Yeah.
I work the, uh-- the lighting board.
- Cool.
- Yeah. [inhales sharply]
Hey, an old Dateline was on last night
about the Ghostface Killers in New York.
Have you, uh-- Have you seen it?
No, I haven't.
It's not as good as the Netflix doc,
but it's decent.
They did a good job
covering the aftermath.
[sighs] Morning.
Hey.
- Did you say anything?
- Mm-mmm.
Did he ask you about Dateline?
It's fine, really.
No, it isn't.
- I told you not to.
- Ow!
- That hurt.
- Good.
I'm a crime junkie, Mom.
It's my-- It's my thing.
[sighs] I'm sorry, Mrs. Evans.
But I really want to start a podcast,
and I think the New York murders
would be a primo first case.
Don't you have rehearsal now, honey?
- Right?
- Yes.
- So you should leave now.
- Right. Yeah. Okay.
- Okay. Great.
- Bye.
- Bye!
- [sighs] I'm sorry.
- It's fine.
What'll you have?
["The Kill" continues]
["The Kill" continues through earbuds]
[Tatum] Hey, wait up!
- [friend] Oh, hey.
- [friend 2] Hi!
- You look hot.
- Where'd you get the jacket?
Thanks. It's my mom's. '90s vintage.
[gasps] You should bedazzle it.
Yes.
Oh! Tonight, my place, party.
I've been stockpiling my mom's edibles.
And you can even invite creepy boy.
Listen, he's not creepy.
- Mmm.
- He's deep.
- And he has a squeezy butt.
- Ew.
The true crime is cringy.
He's obsessed with my mom.
Is your mom gonna let you out
of your cage tonight?
I-- [sighs] I don't know.
Honestly, she's been on overdrive
with the mama trauma.
Well, if anyone has a right
to be insane, it is your mom.
Very true. I've seen all the Stab movies.
Personally, I don't know how
she's not in a psych ward.
[horn honks]
- Oh.
- Look who it is.
- [Ben] Hey!
- Top of the morning!
- Hey, Tay.
- Hey, babe.
- Hiya.
You all need a lift?
- You guys, come on!
- Yes!
- We don't have to walk anymore. Let's go!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Buckle up.
[pop punk music playing]
Buckle up. Buckle up!
[teenagers laugh]
Karl!
Thank you.
- I am so sorry about Lucas.
- No.
It's just you're like a celebrity to him.
You feel like you guys are close, right?
Yeah. I mean, I suppose we've
had to be since it's just the two of us.
Do you ever talk to him about
your life before you had him?
- No.
- No?
No, no. I mean, there's not much I can say
about his abusive asshole father
and how badly our marriage fucked me up.
Why? What's going on?
Oh, I don't know. Uh...
Tatum and I are having
a bit of a rough patch.
She's at that age where
she wants to know about my past.
And as you know,
my past is full of dead people.
Not exactly something
I want to share with her.
So I get quiet, and then she gets loud,
and around and around we go.
Listen. She's your daughter,
and it's natural
she should want to know you.
You know, I just--
I want my kids to be able
to be who they are without living in fear.
I want them to feel safe and protected.
But it's not a safe world, Sid.
And if we protect our children too much,
they'll never learn
how to protect themselves.
[performer] ♪ Be not afraid
Don't run away ♪
♪ In here you're safe
Inside your dreamscape ♪
♪ It's meant to be
I come to thee ♪
♪ So will you come with me? ♪
♪ I'll show you
That you're capable ♪
♪ Of knowing things
You've never known ♪
♪ I promise
Life is beautiful ♪
[Tatum] Oh, fuck! [groans]
[performer] ♪ Beautiful ♪
Watch out!
[screams] Oh, fuck!
[chuckles]
[techie] Sorry.
Fuck me.
I'm stuck!
[teacher] No.
No. Uh, houselights, please.
Where's Aaron? Aaron!
I'm here!
I panicked. I saw Fluffy and freaked.
- Are you trying to kill me?
- I'm sorry.
[performer] Come, get me out.
Get me out of it.
[groans] I can't see anything
through this.
Wardrobe! Chloe!
Oh! Yep, I'm here.
I'm over here. I'm here, I'm here!
My foot keeps on getting stuck
in this dumbass pouch every time.
Okay, diva. Calm down.
Hey, I'm sorry, Hannah.
Oh, no, you're fine.
Trust me, I'm not a real diva.
Just playing the part of one.
But you don't know that. You stay scared.
- Scram!
- [Aaron gasps]
Hannah. Hannah, darling.
[Hannah clears throat]
You and Aaron need to practice.
Uh, Mr. Willis, I missed
my cue. It's my fault.
Tatum... a word.
We need to talk about your Fluffy.
Yeah, I can't see through Fluffy's eyes.
It's more than that.
You're very lackluster.
Fluffy needs energy.
Dogs are lively creatures.
You're too timid.
Tatum, where's your confidence?
You need to bring
more strength to this role.
I'll work on that.
You're Sidney Prescott's daughter.
You need to channel
some of your mother's fire.
I'm surprised really.
I thought you had more grit.
Well, that was rude.
You're playing a dog.
Your only line is "Woof."
It's not that deep.
Hey, fuck him.
Yeah, fuck him.
Ah, don't let Willis get to you.
- Your Fluffy's incredible.
- Thanks, guys.
Um...
Okay, I'm-- I'm gonna go take this off.
I'll help you.
Uh, don't forget. Party tonight.
- My place.
- All right.
- Whoo!
- Mmm!
[chuckles]
[Tatum] Ugh. Get me out of this thing.
- [Ben] I got it.
- [zipper unzipping]
That's it.
["Nothing's Gonna Hurt You Baby" playing]
[sighs]
Am I timid?
Oh, don't let that asshole get to you.
Answer the question. Be honest.
I wouldn't say timid, no,
but you have this really cute shy quality.
"Shy" means "timid," FYI.
Do you think I lack confidence?
[chuckles] I can't win this.
I'm not playing.
[Tatum mutters, scoffs]
- Why do you like me?
- That's a really long list.
Okay. Well, be specific. One thing.
[sighs] No. It's-- It's cheesy.
Say it anyway.
Okay.
I like how you look at me
in a certain way.
And it makes me smile.
Or you say something that makes me laugh,
and I'll go home
and I'll think about it later
and I'll smile and laugh all over again.
I really like that.
That wasn't cheesy.
That was a great answer.
["Nothing's Gonna Hurt You Baby"
continues]
[phone rings]
- Hello.
- [caller] Hello, Sidney.
Guess who. Did you miss me?
I see you found a new town to live in.
It reminds me a lot of where we grew up.
Oh, do we know each other?
[caller] We sure do.
In fact, I was just
in Woodsboro last night.
Things got a little... heated.
But I'm here in Pine Grove now.
Yeah? What brings you here?
[caller] You, Sidney.
You were missed in New York.
It's not the same without you.
I guess you couldn't
be bothered now that you're
so busy with a husband and family.
Well, you sure know a lot about me
for another asshole hiding behind
a fake number and a voice changer.
[caller] Oh, I'm not hiding, Sidney.
Not this time.
[phone chiming]
[inhales shakily]
Surprise, Sidney.
Do you need a minute? Oh! Oh, my gosh.
It looks like you need a minute.
I'll wait.
[scoffs]
Nice try. Stu Macher is dead.
Oh, gosh. I'm gonna agree to disagree
with you there.
[chuckles]
Oh, my God! It is so good to see you.
I always had a thing for you, Sid!
[giggles]
It's gonna be so much fun.
Just like the old days, except now
there's no Billy or Randy or Tatum.
Speaking of whom, your daughter,
her name's Tatum. That is so adorable.
I mean, It's a little weird or whatever,
but it's supercute.
And she is
so pretty.
Do not talk about my daughter.
Oh. Okay, yeah.
[stutters]
I should definitely tell you, though,
I am currently outside of
her high school theater.
Don't you fucking dare!
It's showtime, bitch.
[dramatic music playing]
Hey, Chief.
You're gonna want to hear this.
I just got a call from
the police in Woodsboro.
- [phone buzzes]
- [Mark] Just a sec.
Hey, babe.
[horn honking]
You need to go to the theater right now.
[Mark] What? What--
There's a killer, Mark.
He's going for Tatum.
I'm on it. All available units
to the high school theater now!
- I'm on my way, babe.
- Mark, hurry.
[tires squeal]
[siren wailing]
[rattling]
[door opens]
[ominous music plays]
[Hannah] Start with liftoffs
and landings, okay?
[Aaron] Got it.
Ready?
Ready.
[grunts] Okay, a little hard
on the landing there.
[Aaron] Sorry.
It's just too jerky.
- Softer.
- Got it.
- [clang in distance]
- Huh?
[Hannah] Try it again.
- Okay, any day now!
- Oh.
- [slash]
- [Aaron groans]
Hey, Aaron?
[thud]
Hello?
[scoffs] This is my nice voice.
[exclaims]
Aaron?
Shit.
Aaron? I want to get down now.
[grunting]
Shit.
Hello!
[door opens, closes]
No! No!
[grunts, panting]
Put me down-- [screams]
[panting]
This isn't funny--
[screams]
Aaron!
[grunting, panting]
No! [screams]
Help!
Get me out!
[screams] This hurts!
Aaron!
Hello!
[grunting, panting]
What the fuck?
[screaming]
No, wait!
Shit!
Oh, my God, please!
[screams] No, wait!
Hey, you stay away from me!
Get away!
No, please, wait! [screams]
[screaming, crying]
Please! Please!
Please!
Stop, please! Please, please!
I don't want to die!
[ominous music plays]
[Sidney] Tatum!
Motherfucker!
[dramatic music playing]
- Cover the exits!
- [guards shouting]
[panting]
Oh, God. Okay.
Tatum!
- Mom, what are you doing?
- Oh, God!
- Are you okay?
- Oh, good... okay... okay.
[Sidney panting]
[no audible dialogue]
I wasn't even here. I had already left.
He was home with me.
Okay. Where were you?
I was downstairs in the costume shop.
- [Ben] Not when I was there.
- Wait, you were here?
No, he left and I was there.
But I didn't see you.
I was in the dressing rooms.
The whole time?
No. Not the whole time.
I went home, had a light dinner,
Aperol Spritz.
My God, who would do something like this?
We don't even have an understudy.
- Hey.
So, the killer fled.
Whoever did this
knew their way around here.
It was well-thought-out and executed.
What about the kids?
Did you call your mom?
I called.
The entire Denver police force
is with them, they're safe.
Two teens are dead.
Mark, what the fuck?
[Sidney sniffling]
You are not alone.
We got this.
- If this is Stu...
- It's not Stu.
It's not. He is buried in Woodsboro.
Look, we are taking that
phone call that you recorded,
we're sending it to the state police.
They have the resources
to determine who it is.
We are gonna get him.
Isn't Ben a computer junkie?
[Mark] Aren't all kids?
He applied to Carnegie Mellon
to study computer science.
I hear you. But anybody can do
deepfakes these days.
[sighs]
Why don't you get Tatum?
Just give me a minute and then
we'll get out of here.
[Sidney] Tatum, we're going.
Not you.
- Mom.
- Answer's no.
But, Mrs. Evans--
No.
It's okay. You go with your family.
I'll call you.
Why do you treat him like that?
He's not a killer.
You don't know that.
Not everyone is Billy Loomis.
Just because you can't trust people,
doesn't mean people can't be trusted.
We're not doing this here.
[suspenseful music playing]
- They'll sweep the house.
- Yeah. We'll be quick, Chief.
[deputy] All clear.
We're gonna secure the neighborhood.
Great. We'll only be a few minutes.
- Come on.
- Thank you.
Grab your stuff. You leave in five.
Wait. You're not coming with us?
It's my job to catch whoever's doing this.
[ominous music plays]
[music stops]
Where's your go bag?
I unpacked it a long time ago.
Damn it, Tatum.
[sighs]
So, what? We just run?
Yes, we do.
I thought the great
Sidney Prescott never ran.
With you it's different.
They killed Hannah, Mom.
- We can't just leave.
- Listen, I know this story,
and if we stay, more people will die.
I'm sorry, but I'm not gonna
risk you getting hurt.
Why didn't you warn me?
- About what?
- All of this!
If-If I was ready,
maybe I could have saved her.
Maybe I could have done something.
If you need anything else, pack it.
Mom, why can't you just trust me?
We need to go! Okay?
Here, take these.
Why did you turn the light out?
I thought you did.
[ominous music playing]
Tatum.
Stay behind me.
[Mark whispering] Tatum.
Tatum.
[panting]
Dad.
Please, leave her alone.
Mark, put the gun down.
[Mark] Hon, it's gonna be okay.
Just look at me.
[Sidney] It's me that you want.
You just-- you let her go.
- Drop!
- [Tatum screams]
[Mark grunts]
[Mark yells]
[grunting]
- Mark!
- Dad!
[groaning]
Run!
[panting] This way!
[Tatum] What-What are you doing?
Fuck off!
- Where are we?
- We're safe in here.
- You sure he can't get inside?
- Yeah.
- What is that?
- It's another way out.
I need to get your dad. You stay here.
No, you can't leave me, Mom!
- [thud]
- [screams]
Let me go with you, please!
Okay, hurry.
[Tatum groans]
[whispering] Down to the end. Go.
Okay.
[floorboards creak]
[tapping]
[whispers] Shh.
[gasps]
[screams]
- Mom!
- This way!
[both gasp, scream]
- Mom!
- Go, go, go!
[exclaiming, panting]
[screaming]
Okay.
[both panting]
Shh-- [gasps]
[screams]
Go, go, go!
- [screams]
- Mom!
Go!
[panting] Okay. This way.
[Mark yells]
[grunting]
- Get the police! Go!
- Mom!
Help! Somebody help us!
[grunting]
- Hey, are you okay?
- [panting]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- God, I love you.
- I love you.
[dramatic music playing]
Did I get him?
You got him!
Chad, get the camera now.
Mindy, set up for a remote.
Ma'am, you need to stay
inside your vehicle.
You need to get out of my face.
Mom! Dad!
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Oh, that was horrifying.
- That was awesome.
Grab the camera.
We need B-roll of everything.
You have to be ready at all times.
In my defense, I wasn't exactly expecting
to be part of vehicular manslaughter
the second we roll into town,
but next time...
next time I will be prepared.
[Sidney panting]
Hey.
- Chief, you gonna be okay?
- Put pressure on it.
Just sit still for a minute.
You're bleeding.
Your point?
[emotional music playing]
How's Mark?
It takes a lot to bring him down.
[sighs]
Gale, he said he was Stu.
I'm sorry. What did you say?
Stu.
Stu Macher?
Dead Stu Macher?
Let's unmask this fucker.
[ominous music playing]
- Chief?
- Do it.
Who is that?
I don't know, but I saw him
today in the coffee shop.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
[Mindy] Nobody knows the guy?
Okay, that's weird.
That is weird. It's always
someone you know.
[sirens blaring]
[mysterious music playing]
[indistinct police chatter]
[Chad] You want more B-roll?
We could make a whole movie.
[Gale] I don't know what to say.
I meant to brake and I hit the gas.
Karl Allen Gibbs.
He escaped from Fallbrook
Psychiatric Hospital two weeks ago.
Triple murderer.
Any idea why he'd come after
you or your family?
- No.
- Thanks, Cooke.
Chief.
[sighs]
Well...
He's not gonna hurt anyone else.
No.
This was too easy.
There's always more than one.
Sidney,
Stu Macher is dead.
[sighs]
Watch Tatum for a minute.
[reporter 1] Sidney. Sidney!
One question for you, Sidney!
Can we have a word?
Sidney! What's going on? Over here!
[reporter 2] Can you tell us anything?
What's happening, Sidney? What's going on?
Sidney!
The network texted.
They want us to go live.
- I'll go get Gale.
- No! Don't.
- No. No, I'm not doing this.
- Yes.
They didn't specify it had to be Gale.
- You'll get us fired!
- Do it! Come on!
- Fine.
- [clears throat]
Three, two, one-- Oh, boy.
You try that again,
and I'll rip both your throats out.
- Got it?
- Copy that.
We just learned that Gale Weathers
from the now defunct talk show
Good Morning with Gale Weathers
is in town.
Excuse me, Miss Weathers.
Robbie Rivers, WFPO. May I ask--
- Fuck the fuck off.
- Okay.
You two are a familiar sight.
What are you doing in town?
Just passing through.
With Gale Weathers?
And you just happened
to run over an escaped mental patient
in front of Sidney Evans's home?
What's really going on here?
Why don't you get your own story, Robbie.
Yeah, we're not here to do it for you.
Come on,
give a small-town reporter his big break!
Hey, Sidney.
I'm so sorry this is happening again,
Mrs. Prescott.
Mrs. Evans, Lucas.
Right, yeah. Uh...
Sorry, that's what I meant.
Lucas, do you know anything about A.I.?
A.I.? Uh, I refuse.
That is the death of civilization.
[chuckles]
[Jessica] Why are you asking that?
Just be careful, Jess.
Keep your doors locked.
[Jessica sighs] Okay, come on, let's go.
[gasps]
Oh, you're Gale Weathers. Hey.
- And who are you?
- Uh...
I'm Lucas.
What are you doing here?
He's my son, and we live next door.
- We're friends of the family.
- Hmm.
[Lucas] Yeah.
You like horror movies, Lucas?
Yeah, I lo-- I love them.
Especially the Stab movies?
Yeah, I know them inside and out.
- What are you doing?
- Mom, it's Gale Weathers.
The Stab movies were based on
her true crime bestseller,
The Woodsboro Murders.
I know, but I don't like
the way she's looking at you.
Please leave my son out of
whatever it is you're doing.
Sorry, kid,
but you know how this works.
Yeah.
Everyone's a suspect.
Well, yeah, but you killed the killer.
He's dead.
Hmm.
How do you know there's just one?
Excuse me.
- [scoffs]
- Whoa.
Until this is over, I want you
to stay away from this house.
Come on, let's go.
[Sidney] How did you know to come?
When the news broke about
the two murders at the Macher house,
a flock of reporters
raced to get there, but...
my Sidney-sense told me
that Woodsboro was played out.
Mark is having the recorded calls
analyzed to confirm they're fake.
Is it possible they're real?
Could Stu be alive?
That would be the better story,
but it's... too far-fetched.
[Gale] Hmm.
What's going on?
Oh, I just have
some nerve damage from the...
from the attack in New York.
You're lucky you sat that one out.
It-it was brutal.
Thank you.
It's nice to meet you, Tatum.
Mmm. Tatum?
- Tatum as in...
- That Tatum.
Yeah.
What do you two do for Gale?
We're her hot interns.
Ever since she got axed,
she's been trying to go back to her roots.
So she's rebranding herself
as a crime reporter.
She's teaching us
all she knows about the biz.
- Don't say "biz."
- Yep.
It's more like we're showing Gale
the ropes of making premium content.
Don't say "content."
It's going great.
Except Mindy keeps trying to
steal Gale's thunder.
- I'm the face of the future.
- Sure.
But in the meantime,
we're learning all about fading careers
and failed comebacks.
[Gale] Where are we gonna start?
S-Start what? I'm...
I'm not starting anything.
We have to find out who's behind this.
That guy in the road, Karl Gibbs,
is not some random Killer.
It's always someone
connected to your past.
The police can handle it.
That would be your husband.
And we need to help him.
Don't you want to know who's behind this?
Gale, I can't anymore.
I need to be with my family,
I need to know they're safe.
That's why you need to help me.
Whoever is targeting you
is not gonna stop...
- [phone ringing]
- ...you know that.
Oh, slap my face,
if it isn't the Gale Weathers!
Hi. Oh, my God,
I am so sorry your show got canceled
and then you got fired.
I wasn't fired.
My contract wasn't renewed.
So don't care. Not even a little.
Ugh. I'm so sorry for
running over your friend.
Can't do your own dirty work, Stu?
[mocking blabbering]
Neither can you.
You brought in some old,
irrelevant hag for backup.
It's so sad.
And what happened to the two of you?
You both had so much spunk.
You're gonna die, you A.I. asshole.
We're going to see how fake I am
when I stab you in the fucking throat!
Because I'm coming for you
and I'm gonna love every second of it.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
That was fucking weird.
Fallbrook Psychiatric Hospital.
It's a couple hours away.
We'll start there.
There she is.
I knew you were in there somewhere.
You're right. This isn't
gonna stop unless I stop it.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Mom, I want to go with you.
No, sweetie, it's not safe.
So why are you going?
Because I know what I'm doing.
Mom, please.
You don't have the skill set for this.
Well, then show me.
I don't want to end up like
the other Tatum.
What?
You named me after a girl who
got her head crushed in a garage door.
- She was my friend.
- And she's dead!
She was a-a victim, not a fighter.
I want to be a fighter.
Honey. Listen--
Nice to know what you think of me.
[exhales deeply]
She just lost a friend, so... she's upset.
I want you to keep her away from Ben.
He's not to come over here.
Someone was hiding in the attic.
It could have been him.
We are running traces on all her friends'
cell numbers, emails and IP's.
If Ben or any of her friends
are connected in any way
we're gonna find it.
She's right, you know.
Me protecting her from this,
I made her vulnerable to it.
Right.
Okay.
Okay, Terry. Thanks again.
Woodsboro coroner says there's
no intake form on Stu Macher's body.
The woman who was coroner
in '96 died three years ago,
so there's no one to ask.
So it's a case of lost paperwork?
Or stolen paperwork.
Someone who wants to
make it look like Stu's body
never made it to the morgue.
Or...
It's actually Stu.
- Let's find out.
- Yep.
- Here's your pass.
- Thank you.
Here you go.
Thanks.
How can I help you?
Hi, I'm Gale Weathers.
- I'm a reporter for Channel 7 in New York.
- Mm-hmm.
- We're doing a story on Karl Gibbs.
- figured.
The state police, they were here all night
going through his stuff.
Can we see his room?
Well...
[groans]
Yeah, I guess so. Come on,
it's right down this way.
So what can you tell us about Karl?
He was a pretty violent guy.
Killed three women about 20 years ago.
Can you think of any reason that he would
go after Sidney Prescott and her family?
[Marco] No, not that I know of.
I'm glad you're okay, though.
Thanks.
Did you ever hear him talk
about the Ghostface killings?
Or the Stab movies, or anything like that?
Not that I remember.
What about, um...
him?
Yeah, that's John.
John?
Yeah, as in John Doe.
He didn't know his real name.
He had amnesia from the blow to the head
that gave him all those scars.
When did he arrive here?
Well, it was before my time.
I've been here 16 years.
So late '90s, maybe?
His room was right down there.
You want to see it?
Yes.
You know, h-he was a drifter.
Sleeping on the streets
of California or somewhere.
And then one day he snapped.
Attacked a high school girl.
He was declared incompetent
to stand trial and ended up here.
- And where is he now?
- He was released.
Two weeks ago.
Any idea where he went
after he was released?
No, I'm sorry.
But for that information
you're gonna need a court order.
And I assume that John Doe and Karl Gibbs
spent a lot of time together?
Oh, yeah. No, they were good friends.
Yeah.
[Marco] Very close.
[leaf blower blowing]
Hmm.
[Mindy] Neighbor boy's sus.
He's out there staring at the house.
Not subtle at all.
I've gone back three days.
If the Killer was hiding in the attic,
he had to go into the house at some point.
Could the footage be hacked?
Clearly the killer is tech savvy.
- [Chad] I don't know.
- [clears throat]
Uh, did you two find the towels?
You got everything you need?
Yeah, the water pressure was...
top-notch, so, thank you.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
So, um...
Why are you here?
I'm sorry, I mean, um... [scoffs]
After everything you've been through,
aren't you scared?
[chuckles] Scared. Necessity.
My career trajectory
is to succeed and exceed Gale Weathers.
And as Woodsboro legacy, it is our duty.
Our uncle Randy was
really good friends with your mom.
[Mindy] And I want to uncover
the killer this time.
She has been wrong a lot.
That is not supportive.
Un-Uncover a Killer?
How do you uncover a killer?
Assemble the suspects
and then Agatha Christie
them until they break.
So-- How do you know who they are?
If history is any indication,
it's likely one of your friends.
Probably your boyfriend.
[Chad] Boyfriend's too obvious.
Unless it's by design.
- It's not my boyfriend.
- [chuckles] That's cute.
We need to gather all the suspects
together in one room.
Well, there's a curfew at sundown.
The whole town's closing up.
Actually, there might be a way.
I just would have to figure
out how to get around my dad.
[Chad] Is that possible?
He is the police chief.
But if we can find out who's doing this,
then he can go get them.
If we can help, we should.
I'm sick of being useless.
That was Deputy Cooke.
They're set up to trace his phone
if he calls me again.
So we just have to wait for him to call?
Oh, come on, there's got to be
some way to bait him into calling you.
What if I gave you what you've
been asking me for since 1996?
An interview.
Get the fuck out of here.
Look, I just need an ETA
on that court order.
[Cooke] You got it, Chief.
I'll take care of it.
Good. Okay.
Call me the second Sid's phone rings.
Tatum!
[clattering]
[electrical buzzing]
[screams]
[screaming]
["Red Right Hand" playing]
♪ ...to the edge of town
Go across the tracks ♪
♪ Where the viaduct looms
Like a bird of doom ♪
♪ As it shifts... ♪
[owner] Okay. Get home safe. Bye, guys.
♪ Where secrets lie
In the border fires ♪
♪ In the humming wires ♪
♪ Hey man, you know
You're never coming back ♪
♪ Past this square
Past the bridge ♪
♪ Past the mills
Past the stacks ♪
♪ On a gathering storm
Comes a tall, handsome man ♪
♪ In a dusty black coat
With a red right hand ♪
- Hey.
- Hey, Chlo.
Ben and Lucas are already here.
All right. Uh, this is Chad and Mindy.
Hi. I'm Chloe. Come on in.
[Chad] So your parents own this place.
[Chloe] Yes, but they don't know
we're here, so we got to lay low.
How you doing?
[Chloe] What are we drinking, kids?
Here is...
[singsongy] ...the pepperoni
and mushroom pizza.
- [Tatum] Thanks, Chlo.
- [Chad] Thank you.
So what is the deal with you two?
[Tatum] Um, they want to help us
find out who's doing this.
What, they think it's one of us?
[Mindy chuckles]
Yeah. But I don't.
So this dead dude from thirty years ago,
he is not so dead?
How could Stu Macher really be alive?
Where's he been? Under a rock?
Nobody recognized him for three decades?
That's a ridiculous retcon
for any franchise.
See, this time it is all about nostalgia.
Hey, Min! We talked about the rules thing,
we said we weren't gonna do that anymore.
- We're better than that. So just...
- Sorry. Okay.
So whoever it is wants to
bring Sidney out of retirement.
She's a scream queen. Scream queens
are not allowed to have happy endings.
There's a reason they keep putting
Jamie Lee in new Halloween movies.
We all want to read Wuthering Heights
again for the first time.
But this is real life.
Yes, exactly.
This person isn't a fan of Stab movies,
they're a fan of Sidney Prescott.
Not the Sidney of today, though.
The Sidney of thirty years ago.
The Sidney that was killing Ghostfaces,
like, once a year.
And the reason they're using
Stu Macher to fuck with her
is because he was there at the start.
The night Sidney the Avenging Angel
was born.
[whistles]
Or it really is Stu. I mean,
Billy Loomis had a secret love child,
so who the fuck knows anymore?
- Where'd you get these calls?
- Uh...
My mom's cloud.
Can you tell if they're fake or not?
- If it's a fake, it's a good one.
- Hmm.
The shadows are consistent.
The eyes, hands, they all have
zero artifacts or pixilation. I mean...
These might have been live calls.
All right, well, if it is Stu Macher
then we know he has an accomplice.
He can't be in two places at once, so...
who is it?
Why would any of us want to
terrorize Tatum and her mom?
Why indeed. Let's talk motive.
Pardon. Thank you.
- Okay, Ben.
- Mmm.
Does Sidney truly approve
of you as Tatum's boyfriend?
Moms never like the boyfriend.
That's Mommy 101, there.
And you're an interesting mix
of brawn and brains.
Nah. I like to work out
my body and my mind, yeah.
See, that's incredibly bizarre
to say out loud.
[Mindy] Chloe.
- Hey.
- [Mindy] Fun-loving. Everyone likes.
Excellent hair. Seemingly has no motive.
That's me.
- I'm not buying it.
- [Chloe] Good.
I don't like a girl that everyone likes.
It's boring.
Oh. See? That's motive.
Right? Boredom?
Now we're in Stu Macher territory.
- [Mindy] And you, weird boy.
- Okay.
You've displayed an unsettling obsession
with all things Sidney Prescott.
She's a pinnacle
in the true-crime lexicon.
I'm not obsessed. I'm just...
I'm, uh, fascinated.
Splitting hairs, young man.
Okay, my money's on boyfriend.
Yeah, my bet's on creepy kid.
Okay, I'm pretty fucking sick of
all this "creepy" shit, all right?
I'm not creepy.
Creepy is kind of hot.
[gasps]
- Oh.
- Hey.
Hey.
Can I have another beer?
You can have whatever you want.
[Robbie] And per our discussion,
this is my exclusive.
- That was the deal.
- [Gale] Yeah, yeah. Got it.
- [Robbie] Okay.
- [Gale exhales] There you go.
Oh, okay.
Oh. There.
[Robbie sighs]
All right, I have three cameras on you.
We'll be operating from the control room.
We need your phone, so when he calls...
Thank you.
All right, ladies,
we'll be ready to break into every
affiliate in the state on your go.
Jesus, this is fucking awesome!
[Gale] Okay.
Let's just hope that Stu is watching.
Ready?
- You gonna play nice?
- Of course not.
I've been waiting for this interview
for thirty years.
And three, two...
[theme music playing]
Hi, I'm Gale Weathers
here for an exclusive interview
with Sidney Prescott.
- [phone chimes]
- [Lucas, Chloe chattering]
What the hell?
My mom's going live on TV. Channel 7.
Oh.
- Welcome, Sidney. Hi.
- Hi, Gale.
So everyone knows you as
the survivor of many brutal attacks.
And I understand that you
and your family are once again a target.
Can you explain what's happening?
My family and I
have been attacked twice now
by someone claiming to be Stu Macher.
But Stu was killed in Woodsboro
the night that he and Billy Loomis
attacked you.
Yes, but now I'm not so sure.
Is that why you're doing this interview?
- I want to talk to him.
- What would you like to say?
I want to know what he wants.
Why he's doing this
after all of these years.
I want him to know that
this doesn't need to continue.
Zoom in. Tighter, tighter.
Whatever you need, let's talk.
Hmm.
Maybe he's too much of a little bitch.
He always was the sidekick,
never the lead.
Is that what it is?
You want to be the lead?
Well, here you go.
Call me. You have a platform.
Oh, shit.
Maybe he hasn't tuned in yet.
Let's keep talking.
You and I have known
each other a long time.
A very long time, yes. [clears throat]
How would you describe our relationship?
Complicated but enduring.
You wrote a book, Out of Darkness,
about healing your trauma.
And yet you have completely disappeared
from the public eye for years now. Why?
It just seemed the more
I talked about it, the more darkness came.
Mmm.
You have three children.
Tatum being your oldest. She's seventeen?
I'd rather not talk about my children.
Tatum is the same age that you were
when this whole thing started.
That must have
a huge significance for you.
Like I said, I don't want to
talk about my kids.
[Gale] And you named your kid Tatum
after the young girl who was
brutally murdered all those years ago.
I named her after a childhood friend
whom I loved dearly.
She was the last friend I ever trusted.
Mmm.
Sidney, do you ever worry about
passing your trauma on to your children?
Or, even worse yet,
that they would be
the target of future killings?
Oh, shit.
- [Gale] Sidney?
- Okay, Gale, stop.
- Where's she going?
- Okay, we'll be right back.
Or maybe not. Cut.
All right.
- Um... Go to the outro and stand by.
- [theme music playing]
Wh--
That was unfair.
And dangerous!
But you disappeared, Sid.
People want to know.
I want to know!
- I'm sorry.
- Are you?
What if I had asked you
about Dewey on live TV?
What would you say?
Well, I'd say I'm fine.
Because that's what I tell myself
500 times a day
just to get through the day.
This has been a Robbie Rivers
exclusive with Gale Weathers
and Pine Grove's very own
Sidney Prescott Evans.
We will be monitoring--
That was intense.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry this is happening.
And this-- This was a dumb idea.
How far is the TV station?
I just really want to be with
my mom right now.
We're super close. I mean, I'll take you.
Okay.
[phone ringing]
[breathes deeply]
We're not on air.
- And this needs to be on air.
- Hello?
Aw, Sid, do you need a hug?
[mocking crying]
We've been waiting for you.
Why? So I can stay on the phone
long enough for you to trace the call?
Yes, dumbass! Or you could
just tell us where you are.
Great. I am at Parker's Tavern
with your daughter.
My daughter's not at Parker's.
Well, she's definitely not at home.
[chuckles] She broke curfew.
She's a bad bitch.
I'm gonna punish her.
Fuck.
Is that it? Is he gonna call back?
Because you said this was my story.
- Where's the story, Gale?
- Stop!
You need to call the police right now,
tell them to go to Parker's Tavern.
Sidney!
Oh, fuck.
Mark, Tatum went to Chloe's restaurant.
She's in trouble.
Where are you?
Damn it!
[breathing heavily]
Oh, fuck.
[intense music playing]
Thanks.
- What is this?
- Hmm?
Oh, uh...
- [Tatum] Did you create this?
- [Ben] What? No.
I created that one
just to see if it was possible.
I can't wait to fucking
kill you, Sidney Prescott,
and your daughter.
And I'm gonna love
every second of it, you bitch!
Tate.
- It was you.
- No, it wasn't.
- [groans]
- [gasps]
- Tate.
- [grunts]
You know, not exactly
a roaring success, Min.
We still have no idea who the killer is.
Creepy kid still has my vote.
I'm way too obvious.
So obvious it's not obvious.
What is that smell?
Oh, shit! Pizza's in the oven.
Bathroom break.
We should not have left Tatum
alone with Gen-Z Billy Loomis.
Okay? I'm not feeling good about that.
Do you find it weird
that two very real suspects
just conveniently disappeared?
I really don't want
to get stabbed tonight.
Let's go find Tatum.
Okay.
It's locked. We are locked in.
[sighs] There must be
another way out of here.
Let's try the dining room.
[lights buzzing]
Oven's a piece of shit.
- [sighs]
- [clattering]
[gasps]
Fuck.
[breathing heavily]
Where's the fucking door?
Hey. The kitchen.
There has to be a back door.
[clattering]
That's not good.
[gasps, groans]
[shouts, grunts]
[screams, grunts]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
Aw, shit.
[Mindy] Hey, cupcake!
[groans]
Hey, hey, hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- The killer is in there.
- Hey, hey. I got this.
- Don't go in there.
- It's okay, I got this.
I got this, I got this!
Lucas!
- [Lucas coughs]
- [Chloe] Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
[keys jingling]
- [clattering]
- [gasps]
Fuck.
[footsteps thudding]
[footsteps stop]
[breathing shakily]
[Lucas grunting]
[door opens]
[Chloe] Lucas.
[screams]
[choking, gurgling]
[gasps, groans]
No.
No. Help. No.
No, no, no. No! [coughs]
[groans]
[gurgling]
[crickets chirping]
- [dog barking]
- [Tatum breathing heavily]
No!
[ominous music plays]
Open up, please! Please!
Come on! [grunts]
[suspenseful music plays]
[footsteps approaching]
[shouts, grunts]
Help! Please, somebody help me!
He's trying to kill me! Please!
Someone help me! [shrieks]
[screams]
[grunting]
[music stops]
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music plays]
- [screams]
- I found you.
Did you see him? The killer?
No, I didn't see anyone.
You hit me. Got me real good, too.
We have to get out of here.
Tate, listen.
It's not me, Tate.
I know. I know, I'm sorry.
I would never hurt you, okay?
No!
[alarm blaring]
Help!
[door buzzes]
[Sidney breathing heavily]
[rattling]
[phone rings]
[tense music playing]
Oh, God.
[breathes heavily]
[knocking on door]
[keypad beeping]
[door buzzes]
[grunting]
[Sidney] Oh, God.
[screams]
- [Sidney on phone] Tatum.
- Mom!
I'm coming, okay?
[Tatum, distorted dialogue]
He's at the door!
- Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
- [Tatum crying, distorted]
Oh, fuck you, phone.
[Tatum] I can't hear you!
I can't hear you!
Okay. Okay.
Tatum, listen to me.
I'm not gonna make it in time.
But I'm gonna stay with you.
You need to get the gun. It's in the safe.
[pounding on door]
Okay.
The code is your birthday.
[stammering] I don't know how to use this.
I'm gonna talk you through it.
You have your earbuds?
Well, put them in, okay?
You're gonna need both hands.
[Tatum] Okay.
[pounding]
- Okay. Okay.
- [pounding stops]
Wait.
I don't hear him. I think he left.
No, he's trying to find another way in.
- [pounding resumes]
- Oh, Mom, hurry!
Okay, baby, listen to me.
[stammering] The gun is-- It's loaded,
so you have to turn
the safety off, all right?
You see that little switch?
Flip it up. There's a red dot.
- [gun clicks]
- I see it.
Okay. So all you have to do now
is you point
and you pull the trigger.
You aim for center mass, okay?
And when he goes down,
you shoot him in the head.
[sobbing] I can't.
I'm not like you. I can't.
Tatum, you are.
You are like me.
I saw your interview.
Baby, focus.
We're gonna do this together.
[sobbing]
He killed Ben.
He killed him.
Right now you need to survive. Okay?
That is what's important right now.
[shattering]
[Sidney] Okay.
You're gonna have to shoot him
through the wall.
[Tatum] Where?
[Sidney] Okay, you're gonna
shoot the calendar.
Fire through the calendar. No, wait.
Wait. He's moving.
Mom?
To the right of the door.
Shoot him now! Do it now!
[screams]
Oh, you got him.
[breathing heavily]
You got him.
Okay.
Okay, listen, you're gonna
have to walk around him.
But before you do that,
you shoot him in the head.
But he's dead, I got him.
[Sidney] I know, baby.
You need to make sure.
You shoot him. You shoot him
in the head right now.
[Tatum screams]
Tatum... Tatum!
Tatum!
Mom! Mom!
[grunts]
[Tatum gasps]
[menacing music playing]
[screaming]
[footsteps approaching]
Tatum!
[phone ringing]
[caller] Hello, Sidney.
Are we having fun yet?
If you hurt her...
Relax. I'm not going to hurt her
until you're here to see it.
- Where are you?
- Where the heart is...
until I stab a knife through it.
Come alone.
[breathes shakily]
[Ghostface] Welcome home, Sidney.
We've been waiting for you.
[Stu, distorted] Waiting for you.
Thanks for coming alone.
It makes it so much easier
that you followed the rules.
Stop this shit.
- If you're Stu, show yourself!
- [Stu chuckles]
Where am I?
Can you find me?
It's not really me.
You want to know who I really am?
Remember me?
I'll never forgive you
for what you did to my son.
And you know what?
I would do it again and again.
Your mother destroyed my life.
But let's face it.
She destroyed you, too.
In the same way that you've
destroyed your own daughter.
Fuck whoever you are!
[chuckling]
Over here!
It's me, sis.
Do you want to make a movie?
Oh. How about a scary one?
I've been working on this great script.
Come on, Sid.
We're family.
It really comes down to family,
doesn't it, Sid?
I mean, we both know how far
we'd go for our own family.
And friends, of course.
But all your friends die
for just being near you.
I died for you, Sidney.
Doesn't that mean anything to you?
Where is my daughter?
I thought I'd go back to
where it all started.
A phone call, a girl,
and someone she cares about
tied to a chair outside of her house.
[groans]
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Tatum, baby, I'm sorry.
Just...
What do you want from me? Please tell me.
[groans, sniffles]
You.
Yeah. Me.
Well, me and Karl.
- [Sidney] Karl is dead.
- Mm-hmm.
And I would be, too,
but your daughter missed my head.
You've always got to
shoot them in the head.
Okay, okay.
Isn't that right,
Stu?
[Sidney breathes heavily]
[whimpering]
Okay, okay.
[whispers] I'll be right back.
[grunts]
[groaning]
[grunts, pants]
- [Tatum whimpering]
- Mark.
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
Okay.
[groans]
- [groans]
- [Marco chuckles]
Look at that!
He's still alive.
That is a tough motherfucker.
Fuck you!
Jessica. What?
Hi, neighbor.
How you holding up?
[Marco chuckles]
You didn't really think it was Stu?
Because that'd be dumb. Stu's dead.
You know, alive in spirit, but...
dead.
See, I have a background in AL
I was a Google security specialist
once upon a time. Before Fallbrook.
Bringing Stu back was my idea.
No, no, no, no, it was my idea.
No, I just let you think it was your idea.
Jessica, please, what are you doing?
"Oh, Jessica." "Oh, please."
"Oh, what are you doing?"
God, I don't recognize you.
I mean, what happened to you?
You know, you've really let me down, Sid.
Listen to me. This isn't you.
Whatever this is, there's another way.
Oh, I know.
There's always another way.
[chuckles, grunts] Excuse me.
You taught me that. It's in your book.
You saved my life, Sidney.
Before you ruined it.
You know about my abusive marriage, right?
I was really trapped,
and I couldn't see a way out.
But then I read
Out of Darkness by Sidney Prescott.
Oh, it's such a great book!
And then I realized that your life,
it comes down to one simple truth.
Sidney Prescott kills the bad guy.
That's your purpose.
You are a real-life scream queen.
The final girl.
God, you inspire me!
So I started planning and doing Pilates,
and then I pulled a Sidney
and I killed my husband!
[both chuckling]
[Jessica] I got away with it, too.
And I had you to thank for it. [chuckling]
But then you went away, Sid!
And you didn't go to New York.
A Ghostface attack
doesn't count if you're not there.
You disappeared.
Why, Sidney?
I wanted people to see
there was life after trauma.
But there isn't for you!
Trauma is your life.
When you disappeared,
do you know how much that hurt me?
I mean, I couldn't fucking handle it!
I checked myself into a facility.
Fallbrook. That's where we met.
Okay, I'm talking,
so don't interrupt me, okay?
Great. Fuck. Where the fuck was I?
Shit. Fuck!
New York. Pilates. You disappeared.
- Fallbrook.
- Fallbrook. Fallbrook, yes!
It was the closest psychiatric center
that I could find
because I had to be near you.
And that finally brings us to tonight.
[Sidney] Okay, Jessica, you're right,
I've been selfish.
I can do better. We can start over.
I am starting over.
By killing you.
No more baggage.
I am releasing it all.
What about Lucas? You have a son.
Oh, no, no. He's gone, Sid.
I mean, he was too much like his father.
And now
I can have a new beginning.
Do you think that you've been
a good mother to Tatum?
I mean, you really haven't taught her
anything useful, am I right?
- [scoffs]
- [Jessica chuckles]
You've kept the survivor all to yourself.
But that's okay.
Because I'm gonna teach her!
She's gonna watch her mother die.
Just like you did.
The cycle continues.
No.
[Jessica] You see,
it finally dawned on me.
I don't need you.
I mean, none of us do.
Let's face it, you're kind of
past your prime for a final girl.
I'm creating Sidney 2.0.
Watch closely, Tatum.
Okay.
Okay, honey,
you're gonna need
to call an ambulance. Okay?
What?
Mom! No, wait! Where are you going?
Stay with your dad.
No, no, no, no, Mom! God, no!
[Jessica whispers] Sidney.
Sidney...
Please.
[clattering]
- [boom box blares]
- ["Look Out For Me" playing]
[music stops]
[screams]
[both grunting]
Is that all you've got? [screams]
[screaming]
Fuck!
[Sidney panting, coughing]
Are you okay?
You got to shoot her in the head.
- What?
- Shoot her in the--
Shit!
Damn it. Okay.
Come on.
[screaming]
You okay?
I'm Sidney fucking Prescott's daughter.
Past my prime.
Fuck you.
This is Robbie Rivers with an exclusive
on the scene, live report,
at the home of police chief Mark Evans,
where a bloody nightmare
has come to an end.
[pained grunt]
Network wants a live remote.
No way. Too much blood loss.
I can't hold a camera.
I was hoping you'd do it.
I do feel better.
We're gonna need to frame out
the blood, though.
I'll get the tripod.
Thanks for ditching me.
Seriously, what was that about?
You have always had my back, Gale.
I should have gone to New York.
I should have been there for you.
No, Sid.
And I was wrong about something.
I do trust...
I trust you.
You want me to drive you to the hospital?
- I'd love that.
- Okay.
Just give me a minute.
This is exactly what
I didn't want for you.
I don't think it was up to you.
Tatum was my best friend.
She was funny,
and outspoken.
Said whatever was on her mind.
No edit whatsoever.
And she was strong.
And fierce.
She wasn't afraid of anything.
So that's why I named you Tatum.
Because that was my wish
for you.
To be strong...
and unafraid.
What else can I tell you?
That's enough for now.
Okay.
- You know I love you.
- I love you more.
- Let's go see your dad.
- Yeah.
["Creepin" playing]
Three, two...
It all began last Thursday night
in Woodsboro, California,
at a house made infamous for the stashing.
Cut. I got caught between
"stabbing" and "slashing".
Hey, you suck at this.
Shut up. Go again.
Copy that. Three, two...
Hi. I'm Mindy Meeks-Mar-- I don't know.
[Chad chuckling] You messed up
your own name, dude?
Stop laughing!
Okay. Three, two...
Hi. I'm Mindy Meeks-Martin,
three-time Ghostface survivor
and new reporter for CBS 7, New York.
[Chad] Oh, my God, I wasn't recording
any of that. One second.
[Mindy] I hate you.
["Twisting The Knife" playing]
[music ends]
English (US) - SDH